{
    "question": "4. When did Vira go to Jakarta?    a. Next week\r\nb. Two weeks ago\r\nc. A week ago\r\nd. Last month\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>kak mohon cantumkan bacaan ya klo ada bacaanna. soalnya jawabannya tuh ada dibacaannya </p><p><strong></strong></p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "contoh-paragraf-dalam-kalimat-kalimat-yang-bentuk-present-perfect-253",
            "question": "Contoh paragraf dalam kalimat-kalimat yang bentuk present perfect tense\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Today is 16th August and tomorrow is my sister\u2019s birthday. Her name is Kristal. I want to give her a surprise. I have talked to some of her friends. They have helped me to prepare a surprising party. We have discussed it since July.</p><p>We are going to celebrate my sister\u2019s birthday in a small restaurant near my house. Our parents have also agreed it. The restaurant has been booked by our parents.</p><p></p><p>What about the birthday present? No worries, I have prepared it too. She loves art very much. I have made a painting for her. I hope she will like it. But I haven\u2019t wrapped the painting because it hasn\u2019t dried yet.</p><p></p><p>Have you ever celebrated someone\u2019s birthday?</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "sebulan-rumus-pasangan-kabel-busi-4-silinder-939",
            "question": "Sebulan rumus pasangan kabel busi 4 silinder\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>a month formula for 4 cylinder spark plug wires</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>sorry if wrong</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jonia-driver-3-monts-ago-102",
            "question": "Joni....a driver 3 monts ago\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Joni <strong>w</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>s</strong><strong> </strong>a driver 3 month ago</p><p>(joni adalah seorang supir 3 bulan yg lalu)</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>kalimat nya adalah pola kalimat simple past tense yg menyatakan pristwa di masa lalu.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "this-text-is-for-questions-7-8-announcement-for-all-junior-high-s-418",
            "question": "This text is for questions 7-8    ANNOUNCEMENT\r\nFor all Junior High School teachers\r\nPOSTER COMPETITION\r\nFriday, May 21, 2021\r\n1328 Scott Hall, 11 a.m. - 1 p.m.\r\nYour poster must be:\r\nOriginal\r\nColorful\r\nTheme:\r\nLet's protect ourselves from COVID-19\r\nStay Healthy By wearing Masks\r\nJudges:\r\nMr. Thoms Waldschmidt\r\nMs. Sylvia Hanson\r\n7.What is the onnouncement about?\r\nA.poster competition\r\nB.Teacher competition\r\nC.How to wear mask\r\nCOVID-19 pandemic\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p></p><p></p><p>a. poster competition</p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p>cmiiw ya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "taj-mahal-of-india-isthan-candi-prambanan-of-indonesia-249",
            "question": "Taj mahal of india is...than candi prambanan of indonesia",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Taj mahal of india is <strong>bigger</strong> than candi prambanan of indonesia</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Jawaban dicetak tebal dan menggunakan bentuk komparatif dengan kata sifat (Adjective) satu suku kata sehingga untuk membentuk komparatif harus ditambahkan akhiran -er, menjadi is bigger than. Jawaban tidak mutlak is bigger than, tetapi bisa juga is smaller than atau kata lain yang dianggap lebih sesuai dan lebih valid berdasarkan data pengukuran matematis.</p><p>Semoga membantu ya.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "you-an-old-table-533",
            "question": "You....... an old table\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>You....... an old table\u200b</p><p>You <strong>have </strong>an old table.</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Jawaban pada kalimat di atas dicetak tebal dan merupakan bentuk Simple Present Tense karena menjelaskan fakta. Jika subjek nya adalah kata You, maka harus memakai kata kerja Have yang artinya memiliki.</p><p>Semoga membantu ya.</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "25-pram-what-are-we-going-to-do-after-work-yuni-we-can-ha-555",
            "question": "25. Pram: \"What are we going to do after work?\"    Yuni : \"We can have dinner at the plaza at 7 if you\r\nlike.\"\r\nPram: \"Sounds good. I'll pick you up at 6.30. We\r\nneed half an hour to get there.\r\nWhere will they probably be at six forty-five?\r\nA. At the Plaza.\r\nB. In the office.\r\nC. Still at work.\r\nD. On the way to the Plaza\r\nE. They will meet at Plaza\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>D</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Arti </p><p>Pram : \"Apa yang akan kita lakukan setelah selesai bekerja?\"</p><p>Yuni   :\"Kita bisa makan malam di plaza jam 7 jika kamu mau\"</p><p>Pram :\"Baiklah. Aku akan menjemputmu pada jam 6.30. kita butuh setengah jam untuk sampai kesana.\"</p><p></p><p>karena untuk sampai ke Plaza kira kira pada jam 7.  Maka pada saat jam 6.45, mereka masih otw ke plaza. </p><p><strong>J</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>d</strong><strong>i</strong><strong> </strong><strong>j</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>w</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>b</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>n</strong><strong>n</strong><strong>y</strong><strong>a</strong><strong> </strong><strong>a</strong><strong>d</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>l</strong><strong>a</strong><strong>h</strong><strong> </strong><strong>D</strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "12-they-will-be-here-soon-the-word-they-refers-to-a-nabil-385",
            "question": "12. They will be here soon. The word they refers to ....    A. Nabil and Jaka\r\nB. Jaka and Mrs. Maya\r\nC. Jaka and Gita\r\nD. Erigo and Gita\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>C Jaka dan Gita</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf kalau salah </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "60106how-do-you-read-499",
            "question": "60:10=6.how do you read ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>how do you read? </p><p>1. ask, </p><p>2. continue, </p><p>3. vote, </p><p>4. discuss, </p><p>5. search, </p><p>6. conclude, </p><p>7. don&#039;t be too fast</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu, jadi jawaban terbaik makasih ya</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "it-is-my-pavourite-pet-it-likes-eating-vegetable-it-has-long-ea-126",
            "question": "It is my pavourite pet. It likes eating vegetable. It has long ears\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>jawaban :</strong></p><p></p><p>rabbit......</p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>It is rabbit </p><p></p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>Kelinci memiliki 2 telinga yang panjang dan suka memakan sayuran atau tumbuhan hijau itu sudah menjadi makanan pokoknya.</p><p></p><p>See you at the next asnwer </p><p>Pawuuu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}